<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<description>
  <eprints
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xmlns="http://www.openarchives.org/OAI/1.1/eprints"
    xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.openarchives.org/OAI/1.1/eprints http://www.openarchives.org/OAI/1.1/eprints.xsd">
    <content>
      <text>
        The digital library serves as the Leopoldina's publication server. It provides the Academy and its cooperation
        partners with the organizational and technical framework for the electronic publication of scientific works.
        The publication server includes open access publications, electronic theses, and other documentary publications.
      </text>
      <URL>https://levana.leopoldina.org/</URL>
    </content>
    <metadataPolicy>
      <text>
        All bibliographic metadata provided via this interface, except abstracts, is hereby made available under CC0
        license, free to share and re-use.
      </text>
      <URL>https://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/deed.de</URL>
    </metadataPolicy>
    <dataPolicy>
      <text>
        The electronic documents published on the publication server are subject to applicable copyright law. All
        exploitation rights remain with the authors, unless expressly stated otherwise. Users may only use the documents
        within the scope of the statutory provisions. The publication server is operated by the University of Applied
        Sciences and Arts in Berlin.
      </text>
      <URL>https://levana.leopoldina.org/content/publish/guidelines.xml</URL>
    </dataPolicy>
    <submissionPolicy>
      <text>
        The collection mandate of the publication server includes the storage, cataloging and provision of all
        electronic documents published by the Leopoldina or jointly with its cooperation partners. The copyrights of the
        authors remain fully preserved. Compliance with the copyrights and exploitation rights of third parties is
        the responsibility of the submitter.
      </text>
      <URL>https://levana.leopoldina.org/content/publish/contract.xml</URL>
    </submissionPolicy>
    <comment>
      This institutional repository is powered by the MyCoRe repository software, see http://www.mycore.org/ for more
      information.
    </comment>
  </eprints>
</description>
